SHIVANSH BAJPAI

Ş shiv1ansh | in shivansh-bajpai-1980bb174/ | ⊕ skype:live:.cid.6aa122ea88fd672m | ✓ shivansh.200101@gmail.com +917999743351

About

An enthusiastic student and a skilled professional with a strong ability to lead and calibrate goals across teams and external agencies, able to cultivate and maintain key client relationships and business associations. Additionally, I have extensive experience in business, data analytics, and machine learning.

EDUCATION

MNNIT Allahabad-2024 B.Tech in Mechanical Engineering; CPI - 8.73/10

Intermediate / +2-2019 (CBSE) D.A.V. Public School, SECL, Bilaspur; Stream - PCM/CS; Percentage - 91.8

Matriculation - 2017(CBSE) D.A.V. Public School, SECL, Bilaspur; CGPA - 10

Work Experience

Careervira FEB 2022 - MAY 2022

- Data Analyst

Mentorsity Private Limited NOV 2021 - FEB 2022

- Product Manager

JUNE 2022 - AUG 2022 Amazon

- Amazon ML Summer School '22: Intensive Training program on key ML topics

Projects

RENDEZVOUS 2021

An app for video conferencing and a chat web application with Real-time Chat support, supporting user authentication built from scratch using MERN stack

CrowdGoal 2022

Sentiment analysis for teams participating in FIFA'22 World Cup using data obtained from social networking sites

Position Of Responsibility

1.Lead PR - AVISHKAR '22

2.Lead PR - NEP 2020

3.COORDINATOR(MNNIT Basketball) - BOYS

SKILLS

Programming

- C,C++,C,Python,OOP,Competitive Programming

Web Development

HTML,CSS,JS,BOOTSRAP,MERN stack Developer.

Machine Learning

ML - Algorithms, Predictive Analysis, Data Mining, Clustering, Classification, Web Scraping, Model Development

Additionals

Octave, Matlab, MS Office, Git, SQL, Latex

Languages

Full Proficiency in English and Hindi.